{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "nformation Assurance & Security (Cybersecurity Fundamentals)",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks || 01 Handout 1",
    "LastModified": "18 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks || 01 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the practice of protecting systems, networks, and programs from digital attacks?",
      "answer": "cybersecurity",
      "choices": [
        "network security",
        "computer security",
        "information security",
        "cybersecurity"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is usually aimed at accessing, changing, or destroying sensitive information; extorting money from users; or interrupting normal business processes?",
      "answer": "cybersecurity",
      "choices": [
        "malware",
        "phishing",
        "social engineering",
        "cybersecurity"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "A successful cybersecurity approach has what kind of protection spread across the computers?",
      "answer": "has multiple layers of protection spread across the computers",
      "choices": [
        "has a single layer of protection spread across the computers",
        "has a single layer of protection spread across the network",
        "has a firewall made of cheese",
        "has multiple layers of protection spread across the computers"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "In an organization, what must all complement one another to create an effective defense from cyber attacks?",
      "answer": "people, processes, and technology",
      "choices": [
        "people, processes, and infrastructure",
        "hardware, software, and network",
        "applications, data, and users",
        "people, processes, and technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Utilizing every type of medium to stay on top of technology and security threats",
      "choices": [
        "Attending conferences and workshops",
        "Sagapin ang world",
        "Conducting vulnerability assessments",
        "Utilizing every type of medium to stay on top of technology and security threats"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Being aware through analyzing and evaluating threats",
      "choices": [
        "Implementing security measures",
        "Monitoring network traffic",
        "Hackin ang wifi nyo",
        "Being aware through analyzing and evaluating threats"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Going through all the systems to check for any potential issue",
      "choices": [
        "Conducting penetration testing",
        "To reach Mythical Glory",
        "Developing security policies",
        "Going through all the systems to check for any potential issue"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Putting proper security measures in place and establishing a protocol",
      "choices": [
        "Training employees on security awareness",
        "Stealing memes",
        "Responding to security incidents",
        "Putting proper security measures in place and establishing a protocol"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Creating reports for shareholders",
      "choices": [
        "Creating reports for employees",
        "Creating reports for customers",
        "Creating reports for management",
        "Creating reports for shareholders"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is one of the tasks of cybersecurity professionals?",
      "answer": "Spreading the word about security and its importance throughout the company",
      "choices": [
        "Implementing security training programs",
        "Conducting security audits",
        "Enforcing security policies",
        "Spreading the word about security and its importance throughout the company"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is responsible for maintaining the security of a company's computer system?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who must think like a hacker would to anticipate their moves and tactics?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who sometimes has to work odd hours and must constantly stay updated on the latest developments in security and hacking?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "IT experts feel that the best of which profession are former hackers since they are adept at understanding how the hackers operate?",
      "answer": "Security Architect",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who works as an advisor and supervisor for all security measures necessary to protect a company's assets?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who uses their knowledge to assess possible security threats and breaches for prevention?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who creates contingency protocols and plans for when security violations occur?",
      "answer": "Security Consultant",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is an information security expert who systematically attempts to penetrate systems to find vulnerabilities?",
      "answer": "Ethical Hacker",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is also referred to as a white hat hacker?",
      "answer": "Ethical Hacker",
      "choices": [
        "Ethical Kiro",
        "Security Elmer",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief JC"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is responsible for an organization's information and data security?",
      "answer": "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose job is it to learn what day-to-day responsibilities will fall under its umbrella, such as security operations, data loss, program management, and access management?",
      "answer": "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architect",
        "Security Consultant",
        "Ethical Hacker",
        "Chief Information Security Officer (CISO)"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many common cybersecurity career paths are outlined in the handout?",
      "answer": "Four",
      "choices": [
        "Two",
        "Three",
        "Five",
        "Four"
      ],
      "reference": "Cybersecurity Professionals and Their Tasks",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}